In this video we are going to be creating a primary standard zone, but in our previous video we created a primary standard zone, here you can see we have a
kael standard zone, one which we use a DNS management console, at least then we want to use PowerShell.
So go to your start menu and start PowerShell, asset administrator.
Now you want to use the following command, the add DNS server, primary zone, and the name is going to be a kael standard zone 2.
And the zone file name is going to be the kael standard zone 2.tns, and then dynamic update.
Just exactly what we did for our previous, the first one we created using DNS management console, it's going to be non secure and secure.
So now I want to actually see what we are doing by entering the fair post.
So let those hit run, and at this moment you can see we didn't receive any error message.
And totally see the zone we just created what you need to do, go to your forelock of the zone, and then click refresh.
And here we go, now you can see we have our second standard zone which I had just been created.